Hello?
Hello, Ms. Wang.
I'm with Taotaobao customer service.
My employee ID is 1198.
I'm calling you today
because the children's nutritional powder you bought
might have some issues.
What? There's an issue with the powder I bought?
We are so sorry.
Some levels in this batch exceed safety standards.
First of all,
I want to sincerely apologize to you.
Our company is issuing returns and refunds to all customers,
and providing triple compensation.
Triple is still just over 1,000 yuan.
True, that's not a lot of money to you.
So at the same time,
we are also gifting you a
premium insurance policy worth 3,000 yuan.
The coverage is 5 million.
Thank God this one isn't born yet.
Will it have any effect on my oldest child?
No, it won't.
Just to be safe,
we are gifting you this premium insurance.
All right.
How do I claim this compensation?
Just follow my instructions.
Why does it keep failing?
I apologize, Ms. Wang.
Please wait a moment.
Let me check for you.
Is it done?
Hello?
Yes, I'm here.
I found the issue.
It seems that your...
credit score is too low.
That's why the application failed.
This might be tied to your spending habits.
Do you usually use a credit card?
Never used one.
That explains it.
Because you rarely use credit for purchases,
your credit score is quite low.
Our company, however,
can recommend a few methods
to help raise your credit score.
This is so annoying.
Why is it such a hassle to claim a thousand bucks?
I don't want the money anymore.
Here's the thing, Ms. Wang.
You still need to think about your child.
If there's a problem with this batch of formula,
I mean, just in case...
If your child happens to get sick,
it will be very difficult to treat.
And as you know,
high medical bills can ruin a family.
Ms. Wang,
for the sake of your child,
please reconsider.
All right.
How do I raise my credit score?
Great, Ms. Wang.
I've sent you a few apps.
They contain a few platforms.
Just apply for a loan limit.
Once the loan is approved,
you can just return the money.
Don't worry,
this app is internal to our company.
We have a business license.
I have to apply for a loan?
You're just applying for a loan limit
to help raise your credit score.
Ms. Wang, trust me.
For your child,
a few taps are worth it.
All right.
Damn it.
Hey, Sun Ming.
Check the message I just sent you.
Notify the victims immediately.
I tampered with their accounts.
They won't receive the money for now.
Got it.
Old man.
Awesome.
The number you have dialed is not in service.
Please check the number and try again.
That woman's husband is an executive.
She's on maternity leave.
Getting her to take a loan was super easy.
Got over 200,000 in one go.
What do you mean?
Maternity leave?
She's pregnant?
So what if she is?
Pregnancy brain makes them easy targets.
Might as well scam her.
Damn.
That's just evil!
Quit whining.
Where did all my money go?
No!
That's the money to raise my baby.
What do I do?
Honey?
What's wrong?
Honey, I got scammed.
All our savings are gone.
And I owe over a hundred thousand in loans.
What were you even thinking?
Haven't I always told you to watch out for scams?
How could you still get scammed?
I'm sorry.
Do you know how hard I work for that money?
What about the baby now?
It's all my fault.
My baby...
Mommy is sorry.
Mom.
Ma'am?
Mr. Zhou.
Your wife is out of danger for now.
But we couldn't save the baby.
Please take care of yourself.
It's all my fault.
If I hadn't said those things...
My wife wouldn't be like this now.
What do I do now?
Mr. Zhou, don't blame yourself too much.
At the end of the day, it's the scammers' fault.
My baby...
My baby!
Wang Qin, you still have me.
Wang Qin!
Calm down!
Give me back my baby!
Mom...
Start resuscitation!
Get a doctor, quick!
Mom!
What's the situation?
The victim has passed the critical stage,
but due to the miscarriage, she became highly agitated
and went into shock.
So we have evidence now.
Can we arrest him?
Police! Don't move!
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm a law-abiding citizen!
A law-abiding citizen?
You're coming with us.
Take him away.
Yes, sir.
No, wait!
Wait, what's going on here?
Gu Yan, start talking.
Any leads yet?
The phone you provided was reverse-tracked.
All the important data inside has been deleted.
We can't convict Gu Yan.
We have to release him now.
I finally caught the suspect,
and you're just letting him go?
Calm down.
Without evidence,
this is all we can do.
Sun Ming.
You've really disappointed me.
Li Wen, where are you going?
Leave me alone!
I'm a regular at the station.
What could possibly happen?
Ugh, don't ask.
I don't know why, but lately,
I've been targeted by some punk.
Don't worry.
It won't affect you.
Rest assured.
Gotta go.
You just won't leave me alone, will you?
Let me join the organization.
Beat it!
Come on, you saw my skills, right?
I can clone your phone in under a minute.
You guys definitely need me.
So that was you.
You almost got me killed, you know that?
What, you gonna hit me?
Come on, hit me.
If you don't kill me, I'll keep following you.
Let me tell you something.
If I hadn't just...
If I wasn't trying to avoid trouble today,
I wouldn't care if you're some programmer or engineer.
If you really piss us off,
there's nothing we won't do.
Whatever.
Anyway, I've
got my eyes on you.
Scammers use words, not fists.
Sweetie...
Why are you sitting in the dark so late?
Why couldn't I reach your phone?
I tried several times.
I was working overtime.
You know how competitive things are these days.
I have no choice but to work hard.
Really?
Of course it's true.
You think I want to work overtime?
I'd much rather spend every day with my sweetheart.
You were smoking again.
No.
I really didn't.
It's those heavy smokers at work.
I yell at them every day.
They're just so inconsiderate.
Fine.
Your food is in the pot.
Go to bed early after you eat.
I'm so touched.
Give Dad a hug.
You're filthy.
Take a shower as soon as you eat.
I'm going to sleep.
Okay.
Sweet dreams.
This girl...
She's keeping tabs on me now.
Let's see if I can find some evidence on Gu Yan's phone.
Why is this phone so clean?
Who is she?
Why are there so few photos on her social media?
Looks like Gu Yan is intentionally protecting her.
Maybe we can find some clues through her.